Switched again
He's changing the bride
And she's changing the groom
Things are really
getting interesting now
You were the ones
who told me to sign earlier
Now that I agree to
call off the engagement
What are you panicking for
Don't try to get my attention this way
You misunderstood
If I'm bitter, it's because in the past
I actually valued you so much
She's wearing my wedding ring
And you want the leverage she has
You two really are a match
Sis
I didn't mean to steal from you
Then take off the ring first
Don't make things difficult for Yurou
See
You're the ones who can't let go, not me
right here in your eyes
I don't want Gu Chengze anymore
Then who do you want instead
Miyao, you can't just drag
a random guy into marriage